<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<name>TEB – Subclasses</name>
		<description>All subclasses from The Elements &amp; Beyond (minimal feature stubs for Aurora selection).</description>
		<author>Benevolent Evil (converted)</author>
		<update version="1.0.0">
			<file name="teb-subclasses.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SageZeMage/aurora-teb/main/teb-subclasses.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>
	<element name="Path of the Quake Bringer" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_BARBARIAN_QUAKE_BRINGER">
		<supports>Primal Path</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Path of the Quake Bringer (Barbarian) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_PATH_OF_THE_QUAKE_BRINGER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_STONE_RAGE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_DEMOLISHER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_CLIFF_RUNNING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_SEISMIC_SMASH" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_PATH_OF_THE_QUAKE_BRINGER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_STONE_RAGE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_DEMOLISHER" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_CLIFF_RUNNING" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_SEISMIC_SMASH" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Path of the Quake Bringer" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_PATH_OF_THE_QUAKE_BRINGER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Quake Bringer feature</p>
			<p>To match the grand fury and power of an earthquake or avalanche, barbarians of the Path of the Quake Bringer channel primal power, drawing on the element of earth when they rage to turn their body to stone. These warriors test their strength by smashing boulders and leaping chasms. In battle, they embody the earthquake itself, leaving craters, rubble, and terror in their rumbling wake.</p>
			<p>Quake bringers often come from cultures connected to the earth (especially if they value strength) such as those of {@race Dwarf|PHB|dwarves}, {@race goliath|vgm}, or {@race firbolg|VGM|firbolgs}. {@race Genasi (Earth)|EEPC|Earth genasi} can manifest these abilities using latent elemental power. Some quake bringers communed with earth spirits or spent years in isolation on a mountain to gain power.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Stone Rage" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_STONE_RAGE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Quake Bringer feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level, your rage armors you with rumbling stone. You gain the following benefits while you are raging.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Demolisher" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_DEMOLISHER">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Path of the Quake Bringer feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, your elemental power focuses into mighty blows that smash even stone. You deal double damage with melee weapon attacks to objects and structures. When you hit a target composed of earth (dirt, crystal, stone, metal, etc.) with a melee weapon attack, your weapon is treated as if it were magical for the purpose of overcoming resistance, and if the target is an object or structure, you also gain a bonus to the damage roll equal to half your barbarian level.</p>
			<p>Also, you have advantage on Strength checks made to dig, demolish, or excavate using a tool or object.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cliff Running" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_CLIFF_RUNNING">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Path of the Quake Bringer feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 10th level, you have a climbing speed equal to your walking speed. You don't need free hands to use this speed unless you are climbing a surface that isn't made of some kind of earth.</p>
			<p>In addition, when you jump off of a surface made of earth, you draw power from the earth to boost your leap, increasing your high jump distance by a number of feet equal to your Constitution modifier (minimum+1) and your long jump distance by twice that amount.</p>
			<p>Finally, you have {@sense tremorsense|MM} that extends out to a radius of 60 feet while you are raging, allowing you to sense through the earth (see page 74 for more details).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Seismic Smash" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_QUAKE_BRINGER_SEISMIC_SMASH">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Path of the Quake Bringer feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 14th level, you gain the ability to smash the ground itself and create a great seismic shockwave. As an action while you are raging and wielding a melee weapon, you can strike the ground with this power. Each other creature on the ground within 30 feet of you must make a Dexterity saving throw (DC 8 + your proficiency bonus+ your Strength modifier) You can choose to use a smaller radius, if desired. On a failed saving throw, a target takes bludgeoning damage equal to your barbarian level + your Strength modifier and is knocked {@condition prone}. On a successful saving throw, a target takes half as much damage and isn't knocked {@condition prone}.</p>
			<p>If the ground in the area is loose earth or stone, it becomes difficult terrain until cleared. Each 5-foot radius portion requires at least 1 minute to clear by hand. When you use this ability, you can choose to damage the ground in the area, structures in contact with the ground in the area, both, or neither. This ability deals twice as much damage to those objects.</p>
			<p>Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Path of the Sky Caller" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_BARBARIAN_SKY_CALLER">
		<supports>Primal Path</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Path of the Sky Caller (Barbarian) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_CLOUD_SPEAKER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_PATH_OF_THE_SKY_CALLER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_SKY_SHOUT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_VESSEL_OF_RESONANCE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_SKYBREAKERS_ROAR" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_BREATH_OF_THE_SKY" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_CLOUD_SPEAKER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_PATH_OF_THE_SKY_CALLER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_SKY_SHOUT" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_VESSEL_OF_RESONANCE" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_SKYBREAKERS_ROAR" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_BREATH_OF_THE_SKY" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Cloud Speaker" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_CLOUD_SPEAKER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Sky Caller feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level when you adopt this path, you learn the language of the sky, a necessary step for any sky caller. You can speak and understand Auran. This feature does not grant you the ability to read or write Auran.</p>
			<p>Also, you can speak to the clouds, which relay your messages for you. You can cast the {@spell skywrite} spell from Xanathar's Guide to Everything, but only as a ritual.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Path of the Sky Caller" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_PATH_OF_THE_SKY_CALLER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Sky Caller feature</p>
			<p>The vast sky may seem silent at times, but it has a voice and power of its own, rarely heard by mortals upon the ground. Some barbarians learn through ancient rites to speak or sing to the sky, the clouds and wind, forming a primal connection that enables them to call upon the sky's power in times of need. When they rage, the sky's mighty voice fills their body, allowing them to roar with its thunderous power.</p>
			<p>The first step to becoming a sky caller is hearing the voice of the sky, first as a faint whisper barely distinct from the sound of wind. Many sky callers discover their path high upon a mountain peak, amid a storm, or while practicing tribal singing or shouting rituals.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Sky Shout" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_SKY_SHOUT">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Sky Caller feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, when you enter your rage, or as a bonus action on your turn while you are raging, if you can speak, you can shout with the thunderous force of the sky at a creature within 30 feet of you.</p>
			<p>The target must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, the target takes thunder damage equal to {@dice 1d4} + half your barbarian level, and you choose to either knock the target {@condition prone} or push the target 10 feet away from you. On a success, the target takes half as much damage and isn't pushed or knocked {@condition prone}.</p>
			<p>The saving throw DC for this feature equals 8 + your Constitution modifier + your proficiency bonus. When you reach 6th level, the range for this feature increases from 30 feet to 60 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Vessel of Resonance" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_VESSEL_OF_RESONANCE">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Path of the Sky Caller feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, your connection to the great voice of the sky fills your body with a latent magical voice and transforms it into a vessel for this mighty sound. You have resistance to thunder damage, you cannot be deafened, and magic cannot prevent you from speaking.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Skybreaker's Roar" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_SKYBREAKERS_ROAR">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Path of the Sky Caller feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 10th level, when you target a flying creature with your Sky Shout feature, the range is 150 feet and the target has disadvantage on the saving throw.</p>
			<p>In addition, you can use an action on your turn to roar into the sky above, altering the weather with the power of your voice. You change the weather using the same rules as the {@spell control weather} spell, except you can only do so once, and you can't affect the temperature. You can alter the precipitation and wind by up to two stages up or down, but you can't increase precipitation above stage 4 or increase wind above stage 3. These changes only last for 1 hour.</p>
			<p>Once you have altered the weather in this way, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Breath of the Sky" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_CALLER_BREATH_OF_THE_SKY">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Path of the Sky Caller feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 14th level, you become able to harness the full power of the sky's true voice. As an action on your turn while you are raging, you can release a mighty booming shout in a 60-foot cone.</p>
			<p>Each creature in the area must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed saving throw, a creature takes thunder damage equal to your barbarian level + your Constitution modifier, is knocked {@condition prone}, is pushed 20 feet away from you, and is {@condition deafened} until the end of your next turn. On a successful saving throw, a creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed, knocked {@condition prone}, or {@condition deafened}.</p>
			<p>In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 20 feet away from you by the effect, and the sound of your roar is audible out to 1000 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Path of the Verdant Warden" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_BARBARIAN_VERDANT_WARDEN">
		<supports>Primal Path</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Path of the Verdant Warden (Barbarian) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_PATH_OF_THE_VERDANT_WARDEN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_SYLVAN_AVATAR" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_SPEAK_FOR_THE_TREES" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_CANOPY_TRAVELER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_WILD_REGROWTH" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_PATH_OF_THE_VERDANT_WARDEN" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_SYLVAN_AVATAR" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_SPEAK_FOR_THE_TREES" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_CANOPY_TRAVELER" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_WILD_REGROWTH" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Path of the Verdant Warden" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_PATH_OF_THE_VERDANT_WARDEN">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Verdant Warden feature</p>
			<p>When the forests and jungles of the world are in danger, they must sometimes rely on mortals to defend them. A barbarian of this path has a connection to these verdant places, and calls upon primal spirits to transform them into a treant-like warrior when they rage.</p>
			<p>Some tribes have produced verdant wardens every generation as part of ancient traditions dating back to the time of ancestors. Other wardens learn their ways not from their tribe, but from the forest itself.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Sylvan Avatar" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_SYLVAN_AVATAR">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Path of the Verdant Warden feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, your rage transforms you into an avatar of the forest. Your skin hardens into thick bark, your hair turns to leaves or grass, and your footsteps stir the natural plant life around you.</p>
			<p>While raging, you gain a +1 bonus to AC, you have resistance to radiant damage, and you count as a plant in addition to your other types. In addition, each time you enter your rage, you choose one of the following options to augment your form until your rage ends.</p>
			<p>Your limbs become like the long swaying branches of an elderly oak tree. In this form, your reach with melee attacks and touch effects is increased by 5 feet, and your walking speed is increased by 10 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Speak for the Trees" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_SPEAK_FOR_THE_TREES">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Path of the Verdant Warden feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, you gain the respect of the forest's flora, and they gain respect for you. The magic of this primal bond grants you some benefits:</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Canopy Traveler" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_CANOPY_TRAVELER">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Path of the Verdant Warden feature</p>
			<p>At 10th level, you become attuned to the forests and jungles of the land, and the oldest roads, their branches. You ignore difficult terrain caused by foliage such as plants or fungus, and you have a climb speed equal to your walking speed when climbing trees or other flora, including plants and fungus.</p>
			<p>You can also use a bonus action or an action on your turn to create a length of vine. You choose to create the vine from either your hand or from a point that you can see within 30 feet on a flat and stable surface.</p>
			<p>If you create from your hand, you produce a 60-foot length of untethered vine that acts as tough rope. If you create from a point, you produce a 30-foot length of vine which stretches toward you while staying firmly planted in the surface. The vine can hold up to 1000 lbs, it has 16 AC and hit points equal to 10 + twice your barbarian level and it is vulnerable to slashing damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wild Regrowth" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VERDANT_WARDEN_WILD_REGROWTH">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Path of the Verdant Warden feature</p>
			<p>At 14th level, you draw the energy of nature into you in times of peril. When you begin your turn while raging, if you have no more than half of your hit points left, you regain hit points equal to 2 + your Constitution modifier (minimum 1 hit point1 plus 3 additional hit points if you are in direct sunlight.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="College of Journeys" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_BARD_JOURNEYS">
		<supports>Bard College</supports>
		<description>
			<p>College of Journeys (Bard) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_BONUS_PROFICIENCIES" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_COLLEGE_OF_JOURNEYS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_INSPIRE_URGENCY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_TRAVELERS_LORE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_FROM_THITHER_TO_YONDER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_THE_PLANAR_SHUFFLE" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_BONUS_PROFICIENCIES" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_COLLEGE_OF_JOURNEYS" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_INSPIRE_URGENCY" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_TRAVELERS_LORE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_FROM_THITHER_TO_YONDER" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_THE_PLANAR_SHUFFLE" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Bonus Proficiencies" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_BONUS_PROFICIENCIES">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level College of Journeys feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level, you gain proficiency with one tool out of either {@item navigator's tools|phb}, land vehicles, or water vehicles. If you're already proficient with all of these tools, you gain a tool proficiency of your choice instead.</p>
			<p>Also, your speed increases by 5 feet. When you reach 14th level, this bonus increases to 10 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="College of Journeys" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_COLLEGE_OF_JOURNEYS">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level College of Journeys feature</p>
			<p>Many bards learn of the arcane arts and the skills of the world from books or teachers, but some learn their way about the world by making their way about the world, embarking on journeys like the heroes they tell tales of.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Inspire Urgency" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_INSPIRE_URGENCY">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level College of Journeys feature</p>
			<p>Also at 3rd level, you learn how to inspire your allies to feats of great speed, agility, and drive.</p>
			<p>A creature that has a Bardic Inspiration die from you can use a bonus action on their turn to roll that die, {@action Dash}, and {@action Disengage}. The next time that creature hits with an attack before the end of that turn, the attack deals extra damage equal to the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Traveler's Lore" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_TRAVELERS_LORE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level College of Journeys feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level, you have broadened your horizons and hastened your pace. You never have to reduce your own pace due to encumbrance or terrain while traveling, and if you spend your time while traveling playing an instrument instead of watching for danger, you grant other creatures traveling with you advantage on ability checks made to forage, navigate, or track others.</p>
			<p>Also, when your Spellcasting feature lets you learn a bard spell of 1st level or higher, you can select the spell from the following list, in addition to the bard spell list. You must otherwise obey all the restrictions for selecting the spell, and it becomes a bard spell for you.</p>
			<p>Some bards can learn the {@spell word of recall} spell which is normally only available to clerics. The spell describes "a location, such as a temple, dedicated to or strongly linked to your deity." If you are not using divine magic, you must instead use a location that is a home to you, one of comfort and shelter.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="From Thither to Yonder" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_FROM_THITHER_TO_YONDER">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level College of Journeys feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 6th level, you can use a bonus action on your turn to transport yourself or one willing creature within 30 feet of you that you can see. You teleport the target up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see, and the target can use its reaction to make an opportunity attack against a creature within its reach.</p>
			<p>Also, when a willing creature you can see within 30 feet of you is hit with a melee weapon attack, you can use your reaction to teleport it up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see, forcing the attacker to reroll the attack and use the new result instead.</p>
			<p>You can only use this feature up to a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum once). You regain all expended usages when you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="The Planar Shuffle" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_JOURNEYS_THE_PLANAR_SHUFFLE">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level College of Journeys feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 14th level, you learn how to dance to a magical tune that teleports you around. You can use a bonus action on your turn to activate this ability.</p>
			<p>For 1 minute, at the beginning and end of each of your turns, you may choose to instantly teleport up to 10 feet to an unoccupied space you can see. You can bring along objects as long as their weight doesn't exceed what you can carry.</p>
			<p>You can also bring one willing creature of your size or smaller who is carrying gear up to its carrying capacity. The creature must be within 5 feet of you when you teleport, and must also teleport to an unoccupied space within 5 feet of your destination.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Mountain Domain" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_CLERIC_MOUNTAIN">
		<supports>Divine Domain</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Mountain Domain (Cleric) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_AEGIS_OF_THE_EARTH" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MOUNTAIN_CLIMBER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MOUNTAIN_DOMAIN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_VOICE_OF_THE_MOUNTAIN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MIGHT_OF_THE_OLD_STONE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_DIVINE_STRIKE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_THE_MOUNTAIN_LOOMS" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_AEGIS_OF_THE_EARTH" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MOUNTAIN_CLIMBER" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MOUNTAIN_DOMAIN" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_VOICE_OF_THE_MOUNTAIN" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MIGHT_OF_THE_OLD_STONE" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_DIVINE_STRIKE" level="8" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_THE_MOUNTAIN_LOOMS" level="17" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Aegis of the Earth" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_AEGIS_OF_THE_EARTH">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain proficiency with heavy armor.</p>
			<p>In addition, when you take bludgeoning, piercing, slashing, force, or poison damage, you can use your reaction to reduce the damage you take by an amount equal to 3 + half your cleric level.</p>
			<p>You can use your reaction in this way a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Mountain Climber" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MOUNTAIN_CLIMBER">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, you have advantage on saving throws and ability checks made to climb or keep your footing while on earth or stone, such as when you are climbing a canyon wall, jumping across wobbly stones, or walking along a narrow cliff ledge.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Mountain Domain" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MOUNTAIN_DOMAIN">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>The imposing figure of mountains towering on the horizon and the frightful rumbling of the quaking earth are reminders of the great power shared by mountain and earth gods, and they drive many clerics of these deities to pursue the faith in the first place. Many of these gods (such as Ulaa, Purphoros, and Dumathoin) are diggers and craftsmen that fashion earthen wares out of the mountain's treasures and secrets. Others (such as Skadi and Dunatis) represent the solitude and wisdom of the mountain, whispering truths to their hermit-like clerics upon the peaks. Some are deities of the earth and sand (such as Gaia and Geb), while a few (such as Kurtulmak and Moradin) are the patron gods of earth-dwelling folk like dwarves, goliaths, or kobolds. Clerics of the mountain are as varied as their gods, but all see the resolute, unbending, and stubborn strength of the earth and the mountains as the ideal model to live by.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Channel Divinity: Voice of the Mountain" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_VOICE_OF_THE_MOUNTAIN">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 2nd-level, you can use your Channel Divinity to shake the ground with the voice of the mountain, injuring those who cannot keep their balance.</p>
			<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol and the ground in a 30-foot cube within 60 feet of you rumbles with divine power. Each creature on the ground in the area must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed saving throw, a creature takes thunder damage equal to {@dice 2d6} + your cleric level and it is knocked {@condition prone}. On a success, a creature takes half as much damage and isn't knocked {@condition prone}. Until the end of your next turn, ground in the area is difficult terrain as it continues to quake.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Might of the Old Stone" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_MIGHT_OF_THE_OLD_STONE">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, you become as hearty and stubborn as the earth and mountains themselves, gaining proficiency in Constitution saving throws. If you already have this proficiency, you instead gain proficiency in Strength or Charisma saving throws (your choice).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Divine Strike" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_DIVINE_STRIKE">
		<description>
			<p>8th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>At 8th level, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with divine energy. Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can cause the attack to deal an extra {@dice 1d8} thunder damage to the target. When you reach 14th level, the extra damage increases to {@dice 2d8}.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="The Mountain Looms" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOUNTAIN_THE_MOUNTAIN_LOOMS">
		<description>
			<p>17th-level Mountain Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 17th level, the earth and those upon it quake and tremble within your towering presence. The ground within 10 feet of you is always difficult terrain, and if it was already difficult terrain, it costs a creature 1 extra foot of movement for every 1 foot the creature moves. In addition, creatures that are prone on the ground within 10 feet of you cannot stand up.</p>
			<p>This effect only occurs while you are touching the ground. You can choose to exclude any number of creatures from this effect at any time.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Sea Domain" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_CLERIC_SEA">
		<supports>Divine Domain</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Sea Domain (Cleric) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_BLESSED_WATER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CHOSEN_OF_THE_SEA" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_SEA_DOMAIN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TIDAL_SURGE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CRASHING_WAVES" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_POTENT_SPELLCASTING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CYCLE_OF_THE_TIDES" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_BLESSED_WATER" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CHOSEN_OF_THE_SEA" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_SEA_DOMAIN" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TIDAL_SURGE" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CRASHING_WAVES" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_POTENT_SPELLCASTING" level="8" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CYCLE_OF_THE_TIDES" level="17" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Blessed Water" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_BLESSED_WATER">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, you can spend 1 minute praying over at least 1lb of water to create pure blessed water that lasts for up to 8 hours or until you finish a long rest. You can use this feature up to a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
			<p>You choose one of the following options for the water each time you use this feature.</p>
			<p>If a creature consumes the water, it gains the ability to breathe underwater for a number of hours equal to half your cleric level (minimum of one hour). After you reach 6th level, a creature can drench itself in the water instead of consuming it, granting the creature a swimming speed equal to its speed for a number of minutes equal to 10 x your cleric level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Chosen of the Sea" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CHOSEN_OF_THE_SEA">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain proficiency with the {@item trident|phb}, and you can breathe underwater. You also have advantage on any ability checks relating to bodies of water or water vehicles.</p>
			<p>In addition, you learn the {@spell shape water|XGE} cantrip, from Xanathar's Guide to Everything, and the new {@spell water spout|TEB} cantrip. They are cleric cantrips for you, and don't count against the number of cantrips you can learn as a cleric.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Sea Domain" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_SEA_DOMAIN">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>Gods of the sea—and those of other water sources like rivers or springs—are frequently worshipped in order to make aquatic journeys easier and less dangerous. Many gods of this domain, such as Poseidon, Manannan mac Lir, Thassa, and Njord, are sailors or fishermen rescuing supplicants from shipwrecks and blessing their vessels for travel upon the ocean waves. There are evil gods like Zeboim, Aegir, and Umberlee, who whip the seas into deadly storms, sink ships, and crush coastal settlements with giant waves. Some water gods are avatars of purity, fertility, life, and cleanliness, with temples built at pure springs or sacred rivers, like Sobek or Brigantia. A few like Eadro or Sekolah are patrons of a particular aquatic race such as merfolk or sahuagin.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Channel Divinity: Tidal Surge" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TIDAL_SURGE">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity to create a wave of temporary water around you.</p>
			<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol, and each creature of your choice within 15 feet of you must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes bludgeoning damage equal to {@dice 2d6} + your cleric level, and it is pushed 10 feet away from you or pulled up to 10 feet toward you (you choose which it is each time you use this ability). On a success, it takes half as much damage and isn't pushed or pulled.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Crashing Waves" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CRASHING_WAVES">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 6th level, whenever one of your cleric spells pushes or pulls a creature, you can push or pull it 5 feet further. Also, whenever one of your cleric spells or class features restrains a creature, pushes or pulls a creature into a solid object that's at least one size larger than it (such as a wall, tree, or boulder), or knocks a creature {@condition prone}, you can choose one of the following effects to apply to that creature:</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Potent Spellcasting" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_POTENT_SPELLCASTING">
		<description>
			<p>8th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 8th level, you add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any cleric cantrip.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cycle of the Tides" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEA_CYCLE_OF_THE_TIDES">
		<description>
			<p>17th-level Sea Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 17th level, when you use your Tidal Surge Channel Divinity feature, it deals {@dice 2d6} bonus damage, and the range and distance pushed or pulled are both doubled. At the end of your next turn, another wave of water washes around you and you repeat the effect without expending another usage of Channel Divinity. You can choose new targets and whether to push or pull.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Travel Domain" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_CLERIC_TRAVEL">
		<supports>Divine Domain</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Travel Domain (Cleric) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_BLESSED_STEPS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_BONUS_PROFICIENCY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_TRAVEL_DOMAIN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_SAFE_PASSAGE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_MESSENGER_OF_THE_GODS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_POTENT_SPELLCASTING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_RADICAL_FREEDOM" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_BLESSED_STEPS" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_BONUS_PROFICIENCY" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_TRAVEL_DOMAIN" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_SAFE_PASSAGE" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_MESSENGER_OF_THE_GODS" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_POTENT_SPELLCASTING" level="8" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_RADICAL_FREEDOM" level="17" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Blessed Steps" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_BLESSED_STEPS">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, your journey is blessed by holy purpose. You can use a bonus action on your turn to {@action Disengage}, {@action Dash}, or attempt to escape from a grapple.</p>
			<p>You can also use a bonus action to touch another willing creature and lend it your blessing. At the start of its next turn, it can either dash, disengage, or attempt to escape from a grapple without using an action.</p>
			<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Bonus Proficiency" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_BONUS_PROFICIENCY">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you learn the {@spell message} cantrip, which is a cleric cantrip for you and doesn't count against the number of cantrips you can know as a cleric. You also gain proficiency with one of the following tools of your choice: {@item navigator's tools|phb}, land vehicles, or water vehicles.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Travel Domain" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_TRAVEL_DOMAIN">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>The world is wide and the roads are dangerous. To help guide and guard the mortals who travel, the deities of travel—including Lugh, Sehanine, Marthammor Duin, Hermes, Kruphix, Fharlanghn, and Athreos—teach the proper ways of journeying across the world. They are mostly benevolent and often chaotic. Many serve their fellow gods as messengers or guides. Most wish mortals to travel so as to discover, learn, and live a full life, but some are more ambivalent, representing the mysteries, dangers, and secrets waiting on the horizon. When they aren't exploring new places or acting as messengers for important matters between the churches of other gods, clerics of this domain usually wander.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Channel Divinity: Safe Passage" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_SAFE_PASSAGE">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity to secure magical safe passage.</p>
			<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol, and you teleport one willing creature that you can see within 30 feet of you up to 60 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see. Until the end of your next turn, attack rolls are made against it with disadvantage, and it has resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage dealt by nonmagical weapons. If the target makes an attack, casts a spell that affects an enemy, or deals damage to another creature, the effect ends immediately.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Messenger of the Gods" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_MESSENGER_OF_THE_GODS">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, the spirit of travel fills you and carries you further. You are always under the effects of a {@spell longstrider} spell, and you have advantage on all ability checks and saving throws made to escape from a grapple.</p>
			<p>In addition, at the end of each of your turns, if you are at least 30 feet away from where you were at the start of the turn, you gain a +1 bonus to AC and Dexterity saving throws until the end of your next turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Potent Spellcasting" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_POTENT_SPELLCASTING">
		<description>
			<p>8th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 8th level, you add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any cleric cantrip.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Radical Freedom" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRAVEL_RADICAL_FREEDOM">
		<description>
			<p>17th-level Travel Domain feature</p>
			<p>Beginning at 17th level, you have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and your speed increases by 10 feet.</p>
			<p>Also, you are always under the effects of a {@spell freedom of movement} spell. You can temporarily suppress this effect to cast {@spell freedom of movement} without expending a spell slot or requiring components, unless the effect is already suppressed. You can use a bonus action to end the spell early. The effect remains suppressed until the spell ends.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Winter Domain" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_CLERIC_WINTER">
		<supports>Divine Domain</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Winter Domain (Cleric) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_DIVINE_BLIZZARD" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_HERALD_OF_WINTER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_WINTER_DOMAIN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_ICY_EMBRACE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_COLD_NUMBNESS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_POTENT_SPELLCASTING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_RELENTLESS_WINTER" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_DIVINE_BLIZZARD" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_HERALD_OF_WINTER" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_WINTER_DOMAIN" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_ICY_EMBRACE" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_COLD_NUMBNESS" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_POTENT_SPELLCASTING" level="8" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_RELENTLESS_WINTER" level="17" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Divine Blizzard" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_DIVINE_BLIZZARD">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, you learn how to surround yourself in a momentary blizzard. As a bonus action, you swirl with icy wind and freezing magic. Until the end of your next turn, the area within 10 feet of you is lightly obscured by snow and mist, and when a creature ends its turn within 10 feet of you, you can choose to deal it cold damage equal to your proficiency bonus.</p>
			<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once) You regain all expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Herald of Winter" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_HERALD_OF_WINTER">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain proficiency with heavy armor, and you learn your choice of either the {@spell frostbite|XGE} cantrip, from Xanathar's Guide to Everything, or the {@spell ray of frost} cantrip. That cantrip is a cleric spell for you, and it doesn't count against the number of cantrips you can know as a cleric.</p>
			<p>In addition, you don't suffer the effects of extreme cold, as described in the Dungeon Master's Guide.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Winter Domain" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_WINTER_DOMAIN">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>Clerics who worship a god of ice or winter channel both their god's freezing wrath and tranquil beauty. There are many varieties of winter deities. Some are spiteful and bitter as a winter fey, such as Auril. Yet others, like the Norse deities Uller or Skadi, or the Elven god Rellavar Danuvien, guide their followers through harsh winters and icy terrain with care. Some are better known for their other domains, like nature, trickery, war, or death, such as the Raven Queen, or represent all the seasons including winter, such as Demeter. Most winter gods are cold and distant, but a few are warm and friendly.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Channel Divinity: Icy Embrace" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_ICY_EMBRACE">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you deal cold damage to a creature with a cleric spell or class feature, you can use your Channel Divinity to freeze it with divine will. The creature must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is {@condition restrained} for 1 minute. It repeats the saving throw at the end of each of its turns, ending the effect on a success.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cold Numbness" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_COLD_NUMBNESS">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, you gain resistance to cold damage, and you have advantage on saving throws made to maintain concentration when you take damage or to resist the effects of magical pain (such as the {@spell power word pain} spell).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Potent Spellcasting" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_POTENT_SPELLCASTING">
		<description>
			<p>8th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 8th level, you add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any cleric cantrip.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Relentless Winter" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WINTER_RELENTLESS_WINTER">
		<description>
			<p>17th-level Winter Domain feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 17th level, you gain immunity to cold damage, and you ignore all the effects of exhaustion other than death.</p>
			<p>In addition, you are always coated with protective rime. Whenever you are hit with a melee attack by an attacker within 5 feet of you, if the attacker doesn't have resistance or immunity to cold damage, its speed is reduced by 15 feet and it has disadvantage on weapon attack rolls until the end of its next turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Circle of Seeds" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_DRUID_SEEDS">
		<supports>Druid Circle</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Circle of Seeds (Druid) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_CIRCLE_SPELLS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_CIRCLE_OF_SEEDS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_PLANT_LORE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_RAMPANT_GROWTH" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_SOWING_MAGIC" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_PLANT_FORM" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_VERDANT_MASTER" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_CIRCLE_SPELLS" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_CIRCLE_OF_SEEDS" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_PLANT_LORE" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_RAMPANT_GROWTH" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_SOWING_MAGIC" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_PLANT_FORM" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_VERDANT_MASTER" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Circle Spells" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_CIRCLE_SPELLS">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>Your connection to the plants of the world enables you to easily cast botanical magic. At 2nd level, you learn the {@spell thorn whip} cantrip, and it can't be replaced when you gain a level in this class. At 3rd, 5th, 7th, and 9th level you gain access to the spells listed for that level in the Circle of Seeds Spells table.</p>
			<p>Once you gain access to one of these spells, you always have it prepared, and it doesn't count against the number of spells you can prepare each day. If you gain access to a spell that doesn't appear on the druid spell list, the spell is nonetheless a druid spell for you.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Circle of Seeds" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_CIRCLE_OF_SEEDS">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>The druids who belong to the Circle of Seeds venerate plants and the beginning of life itself. They see plants as the purest expression of life, growth, and the natural world, whether they are vast grasslands, mighty forests, steamy jungles, or lone cacti. They take patient interest in long-term problems and solutions facing the natural world, viewing the world from the timescale of ancient forests and jungles. They view all life as equal, but know that without plants, all life will eventually perish.</p>
			<p>These druids regularly seek the wisdom of dryads and treants and strive to protect the oldest trees and most vulnerable flora in the world from harm. As they journey the world, they often plant seeds where they are needed, revitalizing damaged wilderness and giving life to barren wastelands. In battle, these druids embody the tactics of plants, slowly taking control of the battlefield and establishing traps and hazards using plant magic.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Plant Lore" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_PLANT_LORE">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>At 2nd level, you gain an innate connection to the spirits of the plants of the world, and they have tutored you in their ways. You can understand the speech of plants regardless of language, and any plant that knows at least one language can understand your speech. You also have advantage on ability checks made for knowledge about plants or made to socially influence plants.</p>
			<p>In addition, your druid spells that normally can only target beasts can also target plants.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Rampant Growth" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_RAMPANT_GROWTH">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can summon primal spirits associated with plants to aid you and your allies. As a bonus action, you can magically summon an incorporeal spirit to a point you can see within 60 feet of you. The spirit creates an aura in a 30-foot radius around that point and counts as neither a creature nor an object.</p>
			<p>As a bonus action, you can move the spirit up to 15 feet to a point you can see. It persists for 1 minute or until you're {@condition incapacitated}.</p>
			<p>Once you use this feature to summon a plant spirit, you can't do so again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Sowing Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_SOWING_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, you grow to deeply understand what a plant needs to thrive, and you learn to sow your magical seeds with greater skill. When you use your Rampant Growth feature to summon a plant spirit, you can place the spirit onto any surface, including walls and ceilings, and you can place it in water (requiring no surface).</p>
			<p>In addition, you can spend 1 minute planting a magical seed in the ground using a druidic ritual. You can use a bonus action on your turn to cause a seed you've planted within 30 feet of you to transform and sprout into a plant spirit of your choice, as if you had summoned one with your Rampant Growth feature at that location. You can't move a spirit summoned using this feature, and you can't have more than one of the same type of plant spirit.</p>
			<p>A seed that hasn't been sprouted disappears after 1 hour. You have a number of seeds equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of one), and you regain any expended seeds when you finish a long rest. Once you have used this feature to sprout a seed, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Plant Form" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_PLANT_FORM">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>At 10th level, you gain the ability to shapeshift into a form similar to a dryad - a living, humanoid-like magical plant. As an action, you can expend a use of your Wild Shape feature to transform your body into a plant, rather than transforming into a beast form, and you gain temporary hit points equal to your druid level. While this feature is active, you gain the following benefits:</p>
			<p>These benefits and temporary hit points last for 1 0 minutes or until you use your Wild Shape again.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Verdant Master" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEEDS_VERDANT_MASTER">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Circle of Seeds feature</p>
			<p>At 14th level, you can understand and command plants as easily as a powerful dryad or treant. You can cast {@spell speak with plants} at-will, without expending a spell slot. The spell lasts for the duration or until you cast {@spell speak with plants} again using this feature.</p>
			<p>In addition, when you cast the {@spell awaken} spell targeting a plant, the material components only have to be worth at least S0gp.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Circle of Storms" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_DRUID_STORMS">
		<supports>Druid Circle</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Circle of Storms (Druid) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CALL_THE_WIND" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CIRCLE_SPELLS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CIRCLE_OF_STORMS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_STORM_ASCENSION" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_INNER_TEMPEST" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_HERALD_OF_THE_FOUR_WINDS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_UPDRAFT" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CALL_THE_WIND" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CIRCLE_SPELLS" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CIRCLE_OF_STORMS" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_STORM_ASCENSION" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_INNER_TEMPEST" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_HERALD_OF_THE_FOUR_WINDS" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_UPDRAFT" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Call the Wind" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CALL_THE_WIND">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can use a bonus action on your turn to buffet a target you can see within 60 feet of you with wind. It must succeed on a Strength saving throw against your druid spell save DC or be pushed 5 feet in a direction of your choice. If the target is an unsecured object of size Medium or smaller, it is automatically pushed. If you are not underground or indoors, you push the target twice as far.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Circle Spells" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CIRCLE_SPELLS">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>Your bond with the four winds and the primal storm grants you access to certain spells. At 2nd level, you learn the {@spell shocking grasp} cantrip. It is a druid cantrip for you, and can't be replaced when you gain a level in this class. At 3rd, 5th, 7th, and 9th level you gain access to the spells listed for that level in the Circle of Storms Spells table.</p>
			<p>Once you gain access to one of these spells, you always have it prepared, and it doesn't count against the number of spells you can prepare each day. If you gain access to a spell that doesn't appear on the druid spell list, the spell is nonetheless a druid spell for you.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Circle of Storms" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_CIRCLE_OF_STORMS">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>Druids of the Circle of Storms have communed, through ancient rituals, with the four winds (North, East, South, and West) and with the ancient progenitor of all storms, a magical tempest known as the primal storm. These druids teach that, just like the primal storm, nature is in constant flux, and that this change is a good thing. They anticipate the sudden arrival of a storm or danger at all times, and believe that wisdom involves knowing when to run with the wind and when to run against it.</p>
			<p>Storm druids can often be found in tribal societies that live on open plains, on mountains, or along coasts. Some venerate a particular wind, such as the icy North Wind, or a particular storm, such as the monsoon or the tornado. In battle, they buffet and manipulate their foes with wind and lightning. They invoke the power of the primal storm, rising off the earth to blast their enemies with all of the shocking fury of a thunderstorm.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Storm Ascension" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_STORM_ASCENSION">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to embrace the power of the primal storm. As an action, you can expend a use of your Wild Shape feature to imbue your body with storm magic, rather than transforming into a beast form, and you gain 4 temporary hit points for each level you have in this class. While this feature is active, you gain the following benefits:</p>
			<p>These benefits last for up to 10 minutes, until you lose these temporary hit points, or until you use your Wild Shape again.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Inner Tempest" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_INNER_TEMPEST">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 6th level, whenever you cast a spell of 1stlevel or higher that deals lightning damage or thunder damage while your Storm Ascension feature is active, you roll a {@dice d6}, and you gain a bonus to one damage roll of the spell equal to the number rolled.</p>
			<p>In addition, you have resistance to lightning damage while your Storm Ascension feature is active.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Herald of the Four Winds" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_HERALD_OF_THE_FOUR_WINDS">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>At 10th level, your bond with the four winds enables you to call upon them at a moment's notice. While your Storm Ascension feature is active, you can cast the {@spell gust of wind} spell without expending a spell slot. You can do so as part of the action used to activate the feature. The spell ends immediately if the feature ends.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Updraft" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STORMS_UPDRAFT">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Circle of Storms feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 14th level, while your Storm Ascension feature is active, you can fly up to 20 feet above the ground, instead of only 1 foot. At 18th level, this increases to 60 feet, and your flying speed granted by the feature is also doubled.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Circle of the Land (TEB)" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_DRUID_LAND_TEB">
		<supports>Druid Circle</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Circle of the Land (TEB) (Druid) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LAND_TEB_CIRCLE_OF_THE_LAND" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LAND_TEB_NEW_CIRCLE_OF_THE_LAND_OPTIONS" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LAND_TEB_CIRCLE_OF_THE_LAND" level="2" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LAND_TEB_NEW_CIRCLE_OF_THE_LAND_OPTIONS" level="2" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Circle of the Land" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LAND_TEB_CIRCLE_OF_THE_LAND">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of the Land (TEB) feature</p>
			<p>The Circle of the Land is made up of mystics and sages who safeguard ancient knowledge and rites through a vast oral tradition. These druids meet within sacred circles of trees or standing stones to whisper primal secrets in Druidic. The circle's wisest members preside as the chief priests of communities that hold to the Old Faith and serve as advisors to the rulers of those folk. As a member of this circle, your magic is influenced by the land where you were initiated into the circle's mysterious rites.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="New Circle of the Land Options" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LAND_TEB_NEW_CIRCLE_OF_THE_LAND_OPTIONS">
		<description>
			<p>2th-level Circle of the Land (TEB) feature</p>
			<p>Circle of the Land druids choose a type of land that they hail from, which determines their Circle of the Land spells. In addition to the land options detailed in the {@i Player's Handbook}, there are also druids that hail from deep beneath the ocean, from fiery lands surrounding active volcanoes, from dense and dangerous jungles, or even from the clouds in the open sky above.</p>
			<p>If you are a druid of the Circle of the Land, you also have access to these land options:</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Flame Dancer" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FIGHTER_FLAME_DANCER">
		<supports>Martial Archetype</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Flame Dancer (Fighter) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FLAME_DANCER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FLAME_STANCE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_ALIGHT_IN_FLAME" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FIRE_BREATHING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_IGNITION_STRIKE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_GREAT_COMBUSTION" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_IGNITION_MASTER" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FLAME_DANCER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FLAME_STANCE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_ALIGHT_IN_FLAME" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FIRE_BREATHING" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_IGNITION_STRIKE" level="15" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_GREAT_COMBUSTION" level="18" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_IGNITION_MASTER" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Flame Dancer" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FLAME_DANCER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>The archetypal flame dancer, by means often unknown, has the ability to cover themselves and their weapons in flame. For some, this is through an esoteric breathing technique. For others, this is a strange magical gift. The performance art of fire-eating can lead some to develop these abilities in mundane ways. Many fire genasi and ember dwarves often embrace this archetype, honing their innate flame magic in battle.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Flame Stance" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FLAME_STANCE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, you can wreathe your body, armor, and weapons in magical flames. You can use a bonus action on your turn to enter the flame stance and burst into flames for 1 minute. The flames do not harm you or anything you are holding or carrying, and they can't be extinguished.</p>
			<p>While in this stance, you shed bright light in a 15-foot radius and dim light for an additional 15 feet, you have resistance to cold damage and fire damage, and when you hit a target with a ranged weapon attack using a thrown weapon or with a melee weapon attack, the attack deals {@dice 1d6} bonus fire damage. If you're wielding the weapon in two hands, roll the fire damage twice and use the higher result. You can't deal this bonus damage to each creature more than once per turn.</p>
			<p>Also, while you are in this stance, you deal {@dice 1d6} fire damage at the start of each of your turns to any creature whose space you are fully within, to any creature that you are grappling, and to any creature that is grappling you. If you're fully within a creature's space and one of you is grappling the other one, you deal the creature maximum fire damage instead of rolling.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Alight in Flame" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_ALIGHT_IN_FLAME">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>At 7th level, you learn a trick to sparkle with the glow of flame, helping you hold the attention of others.</p>
			<p>You can use your action to make yourself glow with flame for 1 minute. You shed bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet, and you have advantage on Charisma ({@skill Intimidation}) Charisma ({@skill Performance}) and Dexterity ({@skill Sleight of Hand}) checks when influencing those that can see you. However, you also have disadvantage on Dexterity ({@skill Stealth}) checks.</p>
			<p>You can only use this ability up to a number of times equal to your Constitution modifier (minimum of once1 and you regain all expended usages when you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Fire-Breathing" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_FIRE_BREATHING">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>At 10th level, you learn how to turn your breath into fire as you exhale. You can cast the {@spell produce flame} cantrip at-wil requiring only verbal components.</p>
			<p>You can also cast {@spell burning hands} at a spell slot level equal to your fighter level divided by 3, expending no spell slots and requiring only verbal components. Once you have done so, you cannot do so again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
			<p>Your attack bonus with these spells equals your Constitution modifier + your proficiency bonus, and your spellcasting DC for these spells equals 8 + your Constitution modifier + your proficiency bonus.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Ignition Strike" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_IGNITION_STRIKE">
		<description>
			<p>15th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 15th level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack or deal a creature fire damage, you can choose to light it ablaze. Until a creature takes an action to douse the fire, the target takes {@dice 1d10} fire damage at the start of each of its turns.</p>
			<p>You can use this ability twice, and you regain both uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Great Combustion" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_GREAT_COMBUSTION">
		<description>
			<p>18th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>At 18th level, you gain the ability to ignite living air and transmute the power within into heat. When you would roll fire damage, if one of the targets of that damage is an elemental of the air subtype, you can choose before you roll to maximize up to a number of those damage dice equal to your Constitution modifier (minimum of 1).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Ignition Master" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLAME_DANCER_IGNITION_MASTER">
		<description>
			<p>18th-level Flame Dancer feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 18th level, if you roll initiative and you have no uses of your Ignition Strike feature remaining, you regain one usage. Also, your fighter class features that deal fire damage ignore resistance to fire damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wind Knight" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FIGHTER_WIND_KNIGHT">
		<supports>Martial Archetype</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Wind Knight (Fighter) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_BONUS_PROFICIENCY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_KNIGHT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_STRIKE_TECHNIQUE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_ADEPT_HEARING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WAVE_BENDER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_IMPROVED_WIND_STRIKE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_CYCLONE_STYLE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_STRIKE_MASTER" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_BONUS_PROFICIENCY" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_KNIGHT" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_STRIKE_TECHNIQUE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_ADEPT_HEARING" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WAVE_BENDER" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_IMPROVED_WIND_STRIKE" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_CYCLONE_STYLE" level="15" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_STRIKE_MASTER" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Bonus Proficiency" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_BONUS_PROFICIENCY">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level, your study of air, wind, and sound grants you new insights and draws out your talents. You gain proficiency with one musical instrument of your choice. Alternatively, you learn one language of your choice.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wind Knight" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_KNIGHT">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>The archetypal wind knight can strike with the swirling wind created by their weapons. They use air pressure to transform melee strikes into projectiles, and spin their ranged volleys so that they hit with cyclone force. Wind knight abilities are not magical They follow an ancient fighting tradition focused on the flow of air, sound, and pressure, handed down through generations of masters and devoted pupils. These warriors constantly seek to improve and refine their skili searching for worthy opponents to both test and hone their abilities against.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wind Strike Technique" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_STRIKE_TECHNIQUE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you gain the ability to strike using a weapon with such precision and skill that you can harness the air to your advantage.</p>
			<p>You have four wind strike dice, which are {@dice d8}s. You can decide to use a wind strike die that isn't expended before you make a weapon attack on your turn if you aren't in a liquid or vacuum. This augments the attack, giving it certain benefits depending on whether it is a melee or ranged attack:</p>
			<p>For a melee attack, the reach of the attack is increased by 10 feet, and if the attack is made outside the weapon's normal reach, it counts as both a melee weapon attack and a ranged spell attack and it treats liquids and vacuums as if they were total cover. For a ranged attack, the attack ignores disadvantage caused by long-range or the effects of wind, and the weapon returns to one of your free hands at the end of your turn if it has the thrown property.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Adept Hearing" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_ADEPT_HEARING">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>At 7th level, your awareness of the air currents flowing around you sharpens your hearing to exceptional levels, allowing you to hear things as quiet as the rustle of wind through an illusion or the heightened pulse of a liar. You have advantage on Wisdom ({@skill Perception}) checks and Intelligence ({@skill Investigation}) checks that rely on hearing, and on Wisdom ({@skill Insight}) checks to detect lies if the speaker is within 30 feet of you and you aren't {@condition deafened}.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wave Bender" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WAVE_BENDER">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 7th level, your Wind Strike feature no longer treats liquids as total cover and isn't limited by liquids, and when you augment an attack using a wind strike die, it doesn't suffer disadvantage for being underwater.</p>
			<p>Also, you gain the ability to bend the arcs of your projectile attacks. When you augment a ranged attack using a wind strike die, the attack ignores up to 1 of the bonus to AC provided to the target by cover.</p>
			<p>When you reach 10th level, this number increases to 2, and it increases again to 3 at 15th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Improved Wind Strike" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_IMPROVED_WIND_STRIKE">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>At 10th level, your wind strike dice turn into {@dice d10}s. At 18th level they turn into {@dice d12}s.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cyclone Style" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_CYCLONE_STYLE">
		<description>
			<p>15th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 15th level, when you roll initiative and have no wind strike dice remaining, you regain 1 wind strike die.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wind Strike Master" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_WIND_KNIGHT_WIND_STRIKE_MASTER">
		<description>
			<p>18th-level Wind Knight feature</p>
			<p>At 18th level your mastery over wind-based attacks becomes absolute. When you make a melee weapon attack on your turn and don't augment it using a wind strike die, the reach is still increased by 10 feet. When you make a ranged weapon attack on your turn, you always ignore disadvantage caused by long-range, being underwater, or the effects of wind, and the weapon returns to one of your free hands at the end of your turn if it has the thrown property.</p>
			<p>Finally, your skill becomes so legendary that your Wind Strike feature ignores vacuums.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Way of the Flying Fist" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_MONK_FLYING_FIST">
		<supports>Monastic Tradition</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Way of the Flying Fist (Monk) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_CARRYING_THE_TEAM" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_LEAPING_STRIKE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_WAY_OF_THE_FLYING_FIST" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_INTERCEPTION" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_FLEET_OF_FOOT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_EMPTY_AND_BECOME_WIND" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_CARRYING_THE_TEAM" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_LEAPING_STRIKE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_WAY_OF_THE_FLYING_FIST" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_INTERCEPTION" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_FLEET_OF_FOOT" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_EMPTY_AND_BECOME_WIND" level="17" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Carrying the Team" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_CARRYING_THE_TEAM">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Way of the Flying Fist feature</p>
			<p>Also at 3rd level, you can grapple a willing creature without making an attack, an ability check, or using an action, and when you spend a ki point to use the Step of the Wind feature, you can carry a creature you are grappling your full speed instead of half your speed.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Leaping Strike" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_LEAPING_STRIKE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Way of the Flying Fist feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, you can channel the force of your mighty leaps into your attacks. When you spend a ki point to use the Step of the Wind feature, your jump distance is tripled instead of doubled.</p>
			<p>When you use the Step of the Wind feature and jump or fly at least 10 feet toward a target, you can change the first attack you make against it at the end of the movement into a leaping strike. On a hit, the attack deals bonus damage equal to two of your Martial Arts dice + twice your Dexterity modifier, and you can choose to spend 1 extra ki point. If you do, the target must make a Strength saving throw, falling {@condition prone} on a failure. You only can use this feature with a monk weapon or an unarmed strike, and you can only do so once per turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Way of the Flying Fist" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_WAY_OF_THE_FLYING_FIST">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Way of the Flying Fist feature</p>
			<p>The Way of the Flying Fist teaches that true martial power is found in the air, when one escapes from the pull of gravity. These monks train their bodies to leap great heights, channel that power into their strikes, and even pursue the ancient techniques that enable them to fly through the air.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Interception" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_INTERCEPTION">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Way of the Flying Fist feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 6th level, you can intercept a foe when they move. When a creature moves within 15 feet of you, you• can spend 1 ki point and use your reaction to jump (or fly if you have a flying speed) up to 15 feet to a space adjacent to them. If you do, you make an unarmed attack against the creature immediately at the end of the movement. If you hit, the creature's speed becomes 0 for the rest of the turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Fleet of Foot" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_FLEET_OF_FOOT">
		<description>
			<p>11th-level Way of the Flying Fist feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 11th level, you have advantage on saving throws and ability checks to avoid or escape a grapple or to avoid becoming {@condition restrained}, and you never require more than 5 feet of movement to stand up when {@condition prone}.</p>
			<p>Difficult terrain never costs you more than 2 feet of speed for every 1 feet of movement, and when you spend a ki point to use the Step of the Wind feature, you ignore difficult terrain until the end of your turn.</p>
			<p>Finally, you can move through enemy spaces on any turn you have {@action Dash|PHB|dashed}, {@action Dodge|PHB|dodged}, or {@action Disengage|PHB|disengaged}, but you can't end your turn there.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Empty and Become Wind" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FLYING_FIST_EMPTY_AND_BECOME_WIND">
		<description>
			<p>17th-level Way of the Flying Fist feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 17th level, you have mastered the Flying Fist's ultimate art: becoming weightless and walking on air itself. You have a base flying speed of 60 feet and you can hover. The bonus damage of your Leaping Strike also increases to four of your Martial Arts dice + twice your Dexterity modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Oath of Dynamism" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_PALADIN_DYNAMISM">
		<supports>Sacred Oath</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Oath of Dynamism (Paladin) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_CHANNEL_DIVINITY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_DIVINE_CONDUIT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_OATH_OF_DYNAMISM" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_OATH_OF_DYNAMISM_SPELLS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_TENETS_OF_DYNAMISM" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_AURA_OF_INDUCTION" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_STATIC_CHARGE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_MAGNETIC_FIELD" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_CHANNEL_DIVINITY" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_DIVINE_CONDUIT" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_OATH_OF_DYNAMISM" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_OATH_OF_DYNAMISM_SPELLS" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_TENETS_OF_DYNAMISM" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_AURA_OF_INDUCTION" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_STATIC_CHARGE" level="15" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_MAGNETIC_FIELD" level="20" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Channel Divinity" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_CHANNEL_DIVINITY">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>When you take this oath at 3rd level, you also gain the following two Channel Divinity options.</p>
			<p>When a creature or object within 60 feet of you takes lightning, radiant, or thunder damage, you can absorb the energy as a reaction, using your Channel Divinity. You reduce the damage taken by the target by an amount equal to 5 times your paladin level (to a minimum of O damage) and the target gains resistance to lightning, radiant, or thunder damage (your choice) until the end of your next turn.</p>
			<p>The first time you hit with a melee weapon attack or roll thunder or lightning damage for a spell before the end of your next turn, you deal extra lightning damage to one target equal to your paladin level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Divine Conduit" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_DIVINE_CONDUIT">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, your Divine Smite deals lightning damage instead of radiant damage, and any paladin spells you cast deal lightning damage instead of radiant or necrotic damage.</p>
			<p>When your Divine Smite or a paladin spell you cast deals lightning damage to a fiend or undead, it ignores resistance to lightning damage.</p>
			<p>Also, when you throw a metal weapon as part of an attack, you can magnetically pull the weapon back to you after it hits or misses, causing the weapon to fly instantly back to the hand you used to throw it.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Oath of Dynamism" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_OATH_OF_DYNAMISM">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>The Oath of Dynamism is an ideology of rapid, constant change. Those who swear to the Oath of Dynamism find their divine magic manifesting as light, lightning, and magnetism. Some are warriors of the storm, channeling the raw electric power of a god of lightning into their weapons and armor. Others are pragmatic, modern sentinels of a coming future, ensuring that the march of progress isn't interrupted by those ignorantly afraid of a changing world. Most paladins who swear to this oath are chaotic in alignment, with a strong tendency toward neutrality and self-determination.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Oath of Dynamism Spells" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_OATH_OF_DYNAMISM_SPELLS">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Tenets of Dynamism" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_TENETS_OF_DYNAMISM">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>Because they eschew organized traditions, those who swear to the Oath of Dynamism rarely agree on the words that constitute their ideals. Still, they find themselves alike in following these tenets.</p>
			<p>Like lightning itself, you must never hesitate to take needed action. Deliberation and planning are nothing more than excuses for tardiness.</p>
			<p>Like neglected metal leads to rust and decay, you know idleness only leads to weakness and spiritual immobility. Doing nothing is only for those who can't do anything.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Aura of Induction" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_AURA_OF_INDUCTION">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>At 7th level, you gain an aura like a static field around you and your allies. While you are conscious, you and friendly creatures within 10 feet of you have resistance to lightning damage.</p>
			<p>In addition, whenever an affected creature hits with a weapon attack, you can cause the attack to deal bonus lightning damage equal to your paladin level divided by 3, rounded down. Once you have done this, you can't do so again until the start of your next turn.</p>
			<p>At 18th level the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Static Charge" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_STATIC_CHARGE">
		<description>
			<p>15th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 15th level, when you cast a spell that deals lightning damage or thunder damage, you can add your Charisma modifier to one damage roll of that spell.</p>
			<p>In addition, whenever you expend a spell slot to use your Divine Smite, you are charged with electricity and deal {@dice 2d8} lightning damage to each creature grappling you. The next time you hit with a weapon attack before the end of your next turn, the attack deals bonus lightning damage equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum +1).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Magnetic Field" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DYNAMISM_MAGNETIC_FIELD">
		<description>
			<p>20th-level Oath of Dynamism feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 20th level, you can magically surround yourself in a barrier of magnetic force as an action. For 1 minute, you have a magnetic field that extends 30 feet out from you, granting you the following benefits:</p>
			<p>Once you have used this ability, you cannot use it again until you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Oath of Purification" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_PALADIN_PURIFICATION">
		<supports>Sacred Oath</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Oath of Purification (Paladin) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_CHANNEL_DIVINITY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_OATH_OF_PURIFICATION" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_OATH_OF_PURIFICATION_SPELLS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_TENETS_OF_PURIFICATION" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_AURA_OF_WARMTH" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_PURGE_BY_FIRE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_ERADICATING_FLAME" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_CHANNEL_DIVINITY" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_OATH_OF_PURIFICATION" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_OATH_OF_PURIFICATION_SPELLS" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_TENETS_OF_PURIFICATION" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_AURA_OF_WARMTH" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_PURGE_BY_FIRE" level="15" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_ERADICATING_FLAME" level="20" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Channel Divinity" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_CHANNEL_DIVINITY">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
			<p>When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.</p>
			<p>You can use your Channel Divinity to wreathe yourself in magical golden flames. As an action, you become surrounded with fire that scorches your foes without harming you or your equipment. Each enemy creature within 10 feet of you must make a Dexterity saving throw. A target takes fire damage equal to {@dice 2d6} + half your paladin level on a failed save, or half as much on a success.</p>
			<p>Until the start of your next turn, the flames continue to burn, shedding bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet, and each enemy creature that ends its turn within 10 feet of you takes fire damage equal to {@dice 2d6} + half your paladin level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Oath of Purification" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_OATH_OF_PURIFICATION">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
			<p>In a world teeming with evil and darkness, some crusaders find that revealing evil by the light of day is not enough to stop it—evil must be purged to ashes itself. Growing respect for the cleansing power of divine fire leads these warriors to the Oath of Purification. Known for leading torch-wielding mobs, organizing ruthless inquisitions, and putting evil to the pyre, these paladins are devoted to purity by flame.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Oath of Purification Spells" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_OATH_OF_PURIFICATION_SPELLS">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Tenets of Purification" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_TENETS_OF_PURIFICATION">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
			<p>With their rigid adherence to the concept of purity, those who follow the Oath of Purification rarely deviate from swearing to the purest conceptions of the oath's tenets. The oath emphasizes purity, but its followers run the gamut of alignments based on what they personally believe to be pure and what they see as corruption. The tenets of purification are:</p>
			<p>With darkness comes terror, but with the light of fire comes courage. The purity of my purpose must drive out the uncertainty, fear, and doubt that I encounter.</p>
			<p>Evil and corruption must be cleansed at every turn, no matter the cost. If evil is given time to fester, it will spread like rot or a cancer. And if corruption takes hold within my heart, it must be cleansed before anything else.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Aura of Warmth" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_AURA_OF_WARMTH">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
			<p>At 7th level, you gain an aura of warmth that tempers flame, banishes cold, and purifies toxins. While you are conscious, you and friendly creatures within 10 feet of you have resistance to cold damage, fire damage, and poison damage.</p>
			<p>At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Purge by Fire" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_PURGE_BY_FIRE">
		<description>
			<p>15th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 15th level, when you deal fire damage with a spell or paladin class feature to a creature you can see within 120 feet of you, you can cast {@spell dispel magic} on that creature without using an action, expending a spell slot, or requiring components. You can do this even if you do not have {@spell dispel magic} prepared.</p>
			<p>Once you have used this feature, you cannot use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Eradicating Flame" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PURIFICATION_ERADICATING_FLAME">
		<description>
			<p>20th-level Oath of Purification feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 20th level, you can use your action to ignite one weapon you are holding with divine flame. For the next 10 minutes, while you are holding the weapon, it is magical and engulfed in roaring golden fire. The fire sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. It doesn't harm you or your equipment and cannot be extinguished by normal means.</p>
			<p>Melee attacks you make using the flaming weapon have advantage. When you hit with such an attack, it deals an extra {@dice 1d10} fire damage and {@dice 1d10} radiant damage, and if the target is flammable or is a creature, it is lit ablaze. Until a creature takes an action to douse the fire, it takes {@dice 1d10} fire damage at the start of each of its turns. If damage from the attack or the fire kills a target, that target is burned to ash.</p>
			<p>Once you have used this feature, you cannot use it again until you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Fire Keeper" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_RANGER_FIRE_KEEPER">
		<supports>Ranger Archetype</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Fire Keeper (Ranger) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_CONTROLLED_BURN" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_CULLING_FLAME" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER_MAGIC" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER_SPELLS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_THROUGH_FIRE_AND_SMOKE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_SCATTER_THE_BLAZE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FLAME_WARDEN" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_CONTROLLED_BURN" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_CULLING_FLAME" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER_MAGIC" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER_SPELLS" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_THROUGH_FIRE_AND_SMOKE" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_SCATTER_THE_BLAZE" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FLAME_WARDEN" level="15" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Controlled Burn" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_CONTROLLED_BURN">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, you and objects you are wearing or carrying can't be on fire (except for magical fire such as the {@spell immolation} spell) unless you allow it or you are {@condition incapacitated}, and you can breathe ashes, smoke, and the {@spell stinking cloud} spell without any negative effects.</p>
			<p>In addition, when you cast a spell that lights flammable objects on fire, you can prevent the spell from doing so.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Culling Flame" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_CULLING_FLAME">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>Beginning at 3rd level, you can augment your weapons with flame that not only burns, but destroys other flames, absorbing their heat. As a bonus action, you imbue one or two weapons you are holding with flame, lasting for 1 minute or until you stop holding the weapon.</p>
			<p>The first time each turn that you hit a target with a weapon attack using any imbued weapon, the attack deals {@dice 1d6} extra fire damage. If the target is immune to fire damage and has a body or aura that deals fire damage when hit (such as fire elementals, balors, or azer) the attack deals {@dice 1d8} extra cold damage instead.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Fire Keeper" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>Fire keepers are wardens tasked with protecting towns, cities, and the wilderness from uncontrolled fires and blazes. They harness the power of fire to extinguish or curtail large conflagrations, but they also use controlled flames to clear away dangerous tinder and punish any arsonists they are able to catch. Unlike druids of flame, fire keepers hold no reverence for fire elementals, regarding them only as wildfires; they must be controlled or put down if released into the Material Plane.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Fire Keeper Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, you learn an additional spell when you reach certain levels in this class, as shown in the Fire Keeper Spells table. If the table lists multiple spells for a level, you choose only one of them to learn. The spell counts as a ranger spell for you, but it doesn't count against the number of ranger spells you know. These spells can't be replaced when you gain a level in this class, but instead you can change your decision for one level on the table.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Fire Keeper Spells" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FIRE_KEEPER_SPELLS">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Through Fire and Smoke" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_THROUGH_FIRE_AND_SMOKE">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>At 7th level, you become inured to the effects of the flames you fight to contain, along with the toxic smoke and ash they bring. You gain resistance to fire damage, you have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you don't suffer disadvantage on attack rolls caused by your target being heavily obscured.</p>
			<p>Also, you can use an action or bonus action on your turn to extinguish any nonmagical flames in a 10-foot cube that you can see within 30 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Scatter the Blaze" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_SCATTER_THE_BLAZE">
		<description>
			<p>11th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 11th level, when you deal fire damage to a target using a spell or class feature, you can also deal {@dice 1d6} fire damage to each other creature of your choice within 10 feet of the target. Also, when you deal cold damage to a target using your Culling Flame feature, you can deal {@dice 1d8} additional cold damage to that target.</p>
			<p>Once you have used this feature, you can't do so again until the start of your next turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Flame Warden" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FIRE_KEEPER_FLAME_WARDEN">
		<description>
			<p>15th-level Fire Keeper feature</p>
			<p>At 15th level, you learn how to use flames to defend yourself. When a creature that you can see within 5 feet of you hits you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction to fling sparks at the attacker. It must succeed on a Constitution saving throw against your ranger spell save DC or it is lit ablaze. Until a creature takes an action to douse the fire, it takes {@dice 1d10} fire damage at the start of each of its turns.</p>
			<p>In addition, you defend well against creatures that are ablaze and creatures that have a body or aura that deals fire damage when they're hit with a melee attack. Those creatures have disadvantage on melee attacks against you while you aren't {@condition incapacitated}.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Mariner" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_RANGER_MARINER">
		<supports>Ranger Archetype</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Mariner (Ranger) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_AQUATIC_HUNTER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_MARINER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_MARINER_MAGIC" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_TIDAL_STRIKE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_SEA_TAMER" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_CALL_OF_THE_OCEAN_LORD" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_CLOAK_OF_THE_SEA" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_AQUATIC_HUNTER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_MARINER" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_MARINER_MAGIC" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_TIDAL_STRIKE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_SEA_TAMER" level="7" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_CALL_OF_THE_OCEAN_LORD" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_CLOAK_OF_THE_SEA" level="15" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Aquatic Hunter" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_AQUATIC_HUNTER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>Also at 3rd level, you develop a primal connection to the water and its fauna, granting you benefits. You have a swimming speed of 60 feet, you can breathe water, and being underwater doesn't impose disadvantage on your ranged weapon attacks. When you make a melee attack with a trident, the damage die is increased to a {@dice d8}, or a {@dice d10} if wielded in two hands.</p>
			<p>In addition, you have advantage on any weapon attack made against a creature that's swimming in water, does not have a swimming speed, and can't breathe water.</p>
			<p>Once you reach 7th level, you can also jump out of the surface of water while swimming in it. When you do so, your jumping distance is increased by a number of feet equal to twice your Wisdom modifier (minimum 2 feet).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Mariner" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_MARINER">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>The rangers of the seas and other waters, commonly known as Mariners, swim with the agility and grace of the aquatic wildlife that they share a connection with. They patrol not only the far reaches and icy depths of the ocean, but also the coasts, rivers, and lakes. They hunt those who would corrupt or befoul the waters and track down the aquatic monsters that threaten coastal and underwater settlements.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Mariner Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_MARINER_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, you learn an additional spell when you reach certain levels in this class, as shown in the Mariner Spells table. If the table lists multiple spells for a level you choose only one of them to learn. The spell counts as a ranger spell for you, but it doesn't count against the number of ranger spells you know. These spells can't be replaced when you gain a level in this class, but instead you can change your decision for one level on the table.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Tidal Strike" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_TIDAL_STRIKE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level, you learn how to conjure a ribbon-like wave of crashing water to envelop your weapon strikes. Once on each of your turns when you hit with a weapon attack, you can choose to blast the target of the attack with a wave of water. The attack deals {@dice 1d6} extra bludgeoning damage and if you choose so, the target must also make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, the target is pushed 15 feet away from you.</p>
			<p>The water conjured by this feature is transparent and spiritual in nature, vanishing as quickly as it appears. At 11th level the extra damage increases to {@dice 1d10}.</p>
			<p>You can only push targets using this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Sea Tamer" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_SEA_TAMER">
		<description>
			<p>7th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 7th level, you gain resistance to cold damage, and you have the ability to echolocate like a dolphin or whale. You gain {@sense blindsight} out to a range of 30 feet, but you can't use it while you're {@condition deafened}. The range of this {@sense blindsight} is doubled in water.</p>
			<p>In addition, you can speak with aquatic life. You can comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts, elementals, fey, and monstrosities that can naturally breathe water or have a natural swimming speed, to the same effect as the {@spell speak with animals} spell.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Call of the Ocean Lord" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_CALL_OF_THE_OCEAN_LORD">
		<description>
			<p>11th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>At 11th level, your talent for speaking with marine life grows. You can communicate telepathically with any creature that you can speak with using your Sea Tamer feature, so long as you can see the creature or it is within 60 feet of you.</p>
			<p>In addition, you can telepathically call out across the planes for aid from this marine life. You can cast the new {@spell conjure critters|TEB} spell as a 3rd-level spell without expending spell slots, requiring components, or using concentration. When you do so, the beasts that are summoned must have a swimming speed or the ability to breathe water, and they can't have a flying speed or a burrowing speed. You can choose to summon one CR 1/2 beast instead of two CR 1/4 beasts. No matter your choice, the beasts do not appear until the end of your next turn, and they are not considered fey.</p>
			<p>Once you cast {@spell conjure critters|TEB} in this way, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cloak of the Sea" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MARINER_CLOAK_OF_THE_SEA">
		<description>
			<p>15th-level Mariner feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 15th level, you can conjure a thin cloak of ocean mist, squid ink, or some other kind of aquatic cloud to protect you.</p>
			<p>Whenever a creature makes an attack roll against you, you can use your reaction to cloak yourself. You are heavily obscured for that attack, potentially imposing disadvantage on the attack roll. You must choose to use this ability before the attack roll is made.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Aerialist" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_ROGUE_AERIALIST">
		<supports>Roguish Archetype</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Aerialist (Rogue) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AERIAL_AGILITY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AERIALIST" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_HEIGHT_ADVANTAGE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_NATURAL_ACROBAT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AGILE_KIP_UP" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_STICK_THE_LANDING" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_ACROBATIC_DODGE" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AERIAL_AGILITY" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AERIALIST" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_HEIGHT_ADVANTAGE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_NATURAL_ACROBAT" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AGILE_KIP_UP" level="9" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_STICK_THE_LANDING" level="13" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_ACROBATIC_DODGE" level="17" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Aerial Agility" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AERIAL_AGILITY">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 3rd level, you are capable of incredible flips, jumps, and aerial maneuvers. You have a flying speed equal to half your walking speed on each of your turns. To make use of this speed, you can't be wearing medium or heavy armor. When you end your turn while flying using this speed, you fall unless you can stop the fall.</p>
			<p>In addition, you can choose to calculate your jumping distance using your Dexterity score instead of Strength.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Aerialist" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AERIALIST">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>You have a knack for incredible leaps, falls, and feats of acrobatics. Circus performers, airship sailors, tree-top scouts, and flying characters like aarakocra often follow this archetype. Your tactics usually involve striking from above, leaping over enemies or onto the high ground for better aim. You might even seek that rush of adrenaline that your daring feats bring, always looking for new and more dangerous stunts to slake your thirst.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Height Advantage" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_HEIGHT_ADVANTAGE">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>At 3rd level, you also learn how to tactically exploit any height advantage, gaining an additional way to use your Sneak Attack. You don't need advantage on the attack roll to use your Sneak Attack against a creature if the bottom of your space is vertically higher than the top of the target's space by at least 1 foot for every 3 feet of horizontal distance between you and the target.</p>
			<p>For example, if you are 15 feet away from the target, then the bottom of your space must be at least 5 feet higher than the top of the target's space. If you are 60 feet away, then it must be at least 20 feet higher. If there is 0 feet between your spaces, as there would be if you were making a melee attack with most weapons, then the bottom of your space must simply be above the top of the target's space.</p>
			<p>All the other rules for Sneak Attack still apply to you.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Natural Acrobat" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_NATURAL_ACROBAT">
		<description>
			<p>3th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you gain proficiency in the {@skill Acrobatics} skill. If you already have proficiency in this skill, you gain proficiency with a tool of your choice or learn a language of your choice instead. Also, your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make using the {@skill Acrobatics} skill.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Agile Kip-Up" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_AGILE_KIP_UP">
		<description>
			<p>9th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 9th level, you only use 5 feet of movement to stand up from {@condition prone}. Also, when you're knocked {@condition prone}, you can use your reaction to immediately stand back up and move up to 5 feet to an unoccupied space without provoking opportunity attacks.</p>
			<p>Reducing the damage from a fall can enable you to stay on your feet when you finally land!</p>
			<p>At the end of a fall, a creature takes {@dice 1d6} bludgeoning damage for every 10 feet it fell, to a maximum of {@dice 20d6}. The creature lands {@condition prone}, unless it avoids taking damage from the fall.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Stick the Landing" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_STICK_THE_LANDING">
		<description>
			<p>13th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>At 13th level, the distance you can high jump is doubled, and you can use your reaction when you fall to make a Dexterity (Acrobatics) check and reduce any falling damage you take by the result.</p>
			<p>In addition, the flying speed granted by your Aerial Agility feature is increased by 5 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Acrobatic Dodge" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AERIALIST_ACROBATIC_DODGE">
		<description>
			<p>17th-level Aerialist feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 17th level, you learn how to incorporate your acrobatic maneuvers into your defenses. When you use your Uncanny Dodge feature, you make a Dexterity ({@condition Acrobatics}) check and also reduce the damage you take from the attack (after it has been halved) by the result.</p>
			<p>You can't make this check if you are {@condition prone}, you can't move, or your speed is reduced.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cosmic Affinity" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_SORCERER_COSMIC_AFFINITY">
		<supports>Sorcerous Origin</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Cosmic Affinity (Sorcerer) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_ASTRAL_PHASES" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_AFFINITY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_MAGIC" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_EMPOWERMENT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_STELLAR_NOVA" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_ECLIPSE" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_ASTRAL_PHASES" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_AFFINITY" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_MAGIC" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_EMPOWERMENT" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_STELLAR_NOVA" level="14" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_ECLIPSE" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Astral Phases" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_ASTRAL_PHASES">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Cosmic Affinity feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, you embody the cosmic power of the sun and moon, but only one of them at a time. Choose either the lunar or solar phase. You begin in this phase, and you are always in one phase or the other. After you cast a spell that deals radiant damage, you automatically switch phases at the start of your next turn.</p>
			<p>You can choose to switch phases when you finish a short or long rest and after you cast a sorcerer spell of 1st-level or higher that doesn't deal radiant damage. You can also use a bonus action on your turn and spend 1 sorcery point to switch phases. You can't switch phases more than once per turn.</p>
			<p>The two phases grant you different benefits.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cosmic Affinity" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_AFFINITY">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Cosmic Affinity feature</p>
			<p>Your innate magic is that of the far reaches of the Astral Plane and the Far Realm beyond it, that of the stars, the sun, the moon, and the old things that glide through the dark. Your magical gifts shift through cycles of burning radiance and freezing shadows just as the cosmos itself does. Perhaps you were born under an auspicious star or eldritch constellation. You might be the descendant of a powerful warlock who drew magic from a distant star, or you might have been exposed to the strange magic of the cosmos directly as an adult.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cosmic Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Cosmic Affinity feature</p>
			<p>At 1st level, you learn the {@spell light} cantrip. You also learn additional spells when you reach certain levels in this class, as shown on the Cosmic Spells table. Each spell counts as a sorcerer spell for you, but it doesn't count against the number of sorcerer spells or cantrips you know. These spells can't be replaced when you gain a level in this class.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Cosmic Empowerment" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_COSMIC_EMPOWERMENT">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Cosmic Affinity feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level you learn to strengthen your spells with the power of the astral phase you inhabit. You gain certain benefits based on which phase for your Astral Phases feature you are in.</p>
			<p>While in the lunar phase, you have resistance to cold damage, and when you cast a spell of 1st-level or higher that deals cold or radiant damage, you can add your Charisma modifier to one damage roll of that spell.</p>
			<p>While in the solar phase, you have resistance to fire damage, and when you cast a spell of 1st-level or higher that deals fire or radiant damage, you can add your Charisma modifier to one damage roll of that spell.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Stellar Nova" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_STELLAR_NOVA">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Cosmic Affinity feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 14th level, when you change which phase for your Astral Phases feature you are in, you can spend 3 sorcery points to burst with cosmic power, causing an effect depending on which phase you are entering. The saving throw DC for this effect is your spell save DC.</p>
			<p>Each other creature within 15 feet of you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed saving throw, a creature is {@condition restrained} until the end of your next turn. Also, if you choose, the ground within 15 feet of you becomes frozen by ice, making it difficult terrain for other creatures that lasts for 1 minute. The difficult terrain ends instantly if you enter the solar phase or use a bonus action on your turn to end it.</p>
			<p>Each other creature within 15 feet of you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed saving throw, a creature is {@condition blinded} until the end of your next turn. Also, if you choose, the ground within 15 feet of you becomes lit with golden flames that reach 5 feet high and last for 1 minute. Each creature other than you that ends its turn in the area takes fire damage equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum 1). The fire vanishes instantly if you enter the lunar phase or use a bonus action on your turn to end it.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Eclipse" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COSMIC_AFFINITY_ECLIPSE">
		<description>
			<p>18th-level Cosmic Affinity feature</p>
			<p>When you reach 18th level, you gain the ability to enter a state of cosmic alignment that combines solar and lunar power. As a bonus action, you enter the eclipse state, which lasts for 1 minute. You gain the following benefits while in the eclipse state.</p>
			<p>Once you have used this ability, you cannot use it again until you finish a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Elemental Magic" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_SORCERER_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC">
		<supports>Sorcerous Origin</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Elemental Magic (Sorcerer) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ARMORED_BY_THE_ELEMENTS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_SPECIALTY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_MASTERY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_TALENT" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_PRIMORDIAL_EMISSARY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_TRANSMUTE_BODY" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ARMORED_BY_THE_ELEMENTS" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_SPECIALTY" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_MASTERY" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_TALENT" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_PRIMORDIAL_EMISSARY" level="14" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_TRANSMUTE_BODY" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Armored by the Elements" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ARMORED_BY_THE_ELEMENTS">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, you gain benefits based on your choice for your Elemental Specialty feature.</p>
			<p>At the start of each of your turns, you can choose to deal damage equal to 2 + half your sorcerer level to each creature that is grappling you. Any creature that critically hits you with a melee attack while within 5 feet of you also takes this damage. If you chose Air, this damage is thunder damage; if you chose Fire, it is fire damage.</p>
			<p>Your AC equals 13 + your Dexterity modifier while you aren't wearing armor. If you chose Earth, your body is protected by stone, tough skin, thick fur, soft metal, clay, sand, dirt, crystal, or some other form of earth; if you chose Water, it is protected by mist, coral, ice, sea shells, fish scales, tough skin, a layer of blubber, swirling water, or some other form of water (you choose the form of protection when you gain this feature).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Elemental Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>You manifest magic of the four elements: water, earth, fire, and air. Your magic could be the result of at least one genie in your ancestry, emerging as magical power instead of (or in addition to) making you a genasi. It could be the result of a journey through the Elemental Planes that infused you with magic. Or perhaps you even absorbed an elemental's power in an eldritch ritual.</p>
			<p>You might wield the power of only one of the four elements, or you might pursue all four nearly equally. Every elemental sorcerer begins with a natural talent for one element. Some choose to focus on that element exclusively, while others spend their careers gradually learning how to use all four elements.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Elemental Specialty" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_SPECIALTY">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>Beginning at 1st level, you select one element to specialize in out of the four options: Air, Earth, Fire, or Water. This is your primary specialization, and you gain the benefits listed below for your selection.</p>
			<p>You can hold your breath indefinitely while you're not {@condition incapacitated}, and when you speak, you can choose to speak up to twice as loudly as normal.</p>
			<p>You add your Charisma modifier (minimum+ 1) to any saving throws you make against disease, {@condition petrified|PHB|petrification}, or nonmagical {@condition exhaustion}.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Elemental Mastery" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_MASTERY">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 6th level, you can spend 1 sorcery point as an action on your turn to gain resistance for 1 hour to a particular damage type determined by your choice for your Elemental Specialty feature.</p>
			<p>You gain resistance to thunder damage.</p>
			<p>You gain resistance to poison damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Elemental Talent" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_ELEMENTAL_TALENT">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>Also at 6th level, you gain 3 bonus sorcery points. These sorcery points can't be converted into spell slots and can only be used for metamagic or a class feature granted by this subclass. If metamagic, the option you use must affect a spell of 1st-level or higher, and it must fit certain criteria that are determined by your choice of one of five talents when you gain this feature.</p>
			<p>You regain any unexpended sorcery points when you finish a long rest. You gain an additional one of these bonus sorcery points when you reach 10th level, and again at 14th level and 18th level.</p>
			<p>Choose one of the following options for your talent.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Primordial Emissary" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_PRIMORDIAL_EMISSARY">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 14th level, you know {@spell conjure elemental} and {@spell conjure minor elementals} as sorcerer spells, and they don't count against the number of sorcerer spells you can learn. As an action, you can spend 4 sorcery points to cast conjure minor elementals or 5 sorcery points to cast conjure elemental, without expending a spell slot. You can cast conjure minor elementals once as an action without expending a spell slot or sorcery points, and you regain the ability to do so when you finish a long rest.</p>
			<p>When you cast a spell that summons or creates an elemental, you gain a bonus to any Constitution saving throws you make to maintain concentration on the spell equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum+ 1).</p>
			<p>In addition, you can speak, read, and write Primordial. Knowing this language allows you to understand and be understood by those speaking its dialects: Aquan, Auran, lgnan, and Terran. Whenever you make a Charisma check when interacting with elementals, your proficiency bonus is doubled if it applies to the check.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Transmute Body" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ELEMENTAL_MAGIC_TRANSMUTE_BODY">
		<description>
			<p>18th-level Elemental Magic feature</p>
			<p>At 18th level, your body becomes a vessel for elemental magic, and you choose one of the following elementals: air elemental, earth elemental, fire elemental, or water elemental. You can spend 4 sorcery points as an action on your turn to transform into that element.</p>
			<p>For 1 minute, your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of your chosen elemental, but you retain your size, hit points, alignment, personality, and your Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You retain your AC if it is higher than your new form's. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, and the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source. You can still speak, use your hands, and cast spells. Your equipment is unharmed by your new form and you can use it as normal.</p>
			<p>The transformation ends early if you are incapacitated, if you die, or if you dismiss it as a bonus action. Once you have used this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Green Thumb" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_SORCERER_GREEN_THUMB">
		<supports>Sorcerous Origin</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Green Thumb (Sorcerer) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_BLOOMING_VITALITY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_BOTANICAL_MASTERY" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_GREEN_THUMB" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_PLANT_MAGIC" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_SPELL_SEEDS" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_VERDUROUS_SOUL" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_TREE_OF_MAGIC" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_BLOOMING_VITALITY" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_BOTANICAL_MASTERY" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_GREEN_THUMB" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_PLANT_MAGIC" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_SPELL_SEEDS" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_VERDUROUS_SOUL" level="14" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_TREE_OF_MAGIC" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Blooming Vitality" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_BLOOMING_VITALITY">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>Beginning at 1st level, you rest as deeply as a plant, and you bloom with verdant life. When you are struck, this extra vitality wilts, but it will bloom again in time.</p>
			<p>Whenever you finish a long rest, you gain temporary hit points equal to half your sorcerer level (minimum 1).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Botanical Mastery" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_BOTANICAL_MASTERY">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>Also at 1st level, you know how to make the most of your connection to plants. When you cast the {@spell thorn whip} or {@spell razor leaf|TEB} cantrips, you roll the same number of damage dice as normal, but they are {@dice d10}s instead of {@dice d6}s.</p>
			<p>When you cast the new {@spell leaf shield|TEB} spell you are considered proficient with the shield you create while you are wielding it without using any hands.</p>
			<p>Finally, you have advantage on ability checks made to cultivate or tend to plants or to socially interact with plant creatures.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Green Thumb" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_GREEN_THUMB">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>You carry an innate magic connected to the spirits of nature and flora, such as plants and fungi. There might be dryads among your ancestors, or your mother could have been infested with a magical fungus when you were in the womb. Maybe you were born in a druid's grove during a solstice, or perhaps you were touched by the magic of an archfey as a young child.</p>
			<p>The primal power that flows within you will inevitably affect you and your surroundings. Many sorcerers of the green thumb find from childhood that they are different, and as they age, the oddities only grow.</p>
			<p>At your option, you can pick from or roll on the Green Magic Quirks table to create a quirk for your character.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Plant Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_PLANT_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 1st level, you add both the new {@spell razor leaf|TEB} cantrip and the {@spell thorn whip} cantrip to your sorcerer class spell list. You also learn additional spells when you reach certain levels in this class, as shown on the Plant Spells table. Each spell counts as a sorcerer spell for you, but it doesn't count against the number of sorcerer spells or cantrips you know. These spells can't be replaced when you gain a level in this class.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Spell Seeds" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_SPELL_SEEDS">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>At 6th level, you gain the ability to plant magic seeds in the wounds of your enemies to sprout into sorcery.</p>
			<p>When you deal a creature force, necrotic, piercing, poison, or slashing damage using a sorcerer spell, you can pay 1 sorcery point to plant a hidden magical seed in the creature that lasts until you finish a long rest. While a creature is seeded by you, you cannot plant any additional magical seeds in it.</p>
			<p>As an action, you can choose one creature that you have seeded, causing the seed to sprout from its body and bloom into magic. You cast a spell that has a casting time of 1 action or bonus action, expending spell slots and requiring components as normal, but the spell is cast from the seed's location instead of your own.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Verdurous Soul" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_VERDUROUS_SOUL">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>At 14th level, you learn to restore your body by drawing power from nature as plants do. You can use a bonus action and spend 1 to 5 sorcery points while you are within bright light or a body of water, regaining {@dice 3d6} hit points for each sorcery point spent. Either the light must be sunlight, or the water must be clean enough to see through and not acidic enough to deal damage.</p>
			<p>Also, when you take a short rest in such a place, you can regain a number of hit points equal to your sorcerer level + your Charisma modifier. Once you do, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</p>
			<p>Finally, you can feed yourself for a day without eating anything by staying in both sunlight and clean water at the same time for at least 1 hour.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Tree of Magic" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_GREEN_THUMB_TREE_OF_MAGIC">
		<description>
			<p>18th-level Green Thumb feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 18th level, you can use an action on your turn to plant a magical tree in an unoccupied space within 5 feet of you. The tree grows instantly to full size: its trunk is 3 feet in diameter and occupies its space, and the tree is up to 20 feet tali but obstacles can constrain its height. The tree glows with magic and it is immune to damage, but it is still a physical object. It is tangible, it provides cover, it can be climbed, etc.</p>
			<p>When the tree appears, you can imbue the tree with one sorcerer spell you know of 5th-level or lower, but you must spend sorcery points equal to the spell's level to do so. The spell must target only one creature and it can't be a cantrip or have a range of Self.</p>
			<p>The tree lasts for 1 minute or until you lose your concentration (as if you were concentrating on a spell), and it provides the following benefits for the duration.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="The Dragon" type="Archetype" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_WARLOCK_THE_DRAGON">
		<supports>Otherworldly Patron</supports>
		<description>
			<p>The Dragon (Warlock) from The Elements &amp;amp; Beyond. (Converted minimal feature stubs.)</p>
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_ARMOR_OF_THE_WYRM" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_BREATH_OF_THE_WYRM" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_EXPANDED_SPELL_LIST" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_THE_DRAGON" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_DRACONIC_ESSENCE" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_EVERLASTING_SCALES" />
			<div element="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_WINGS_OF_TERROR" />
		</description>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_ARMOR_OF_THE_WYRM" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_BREATH_OF_THE_WYRM" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_EXPANDED_SPELL_LIST" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_THE_DRAGON" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_DRACONIC_ESSENCE" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_EVERLASTING_SCALES" level="10" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_WINGS_OF_TERROR" level="14" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	<element name="Armor of the Wyrm" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_ARMOR_OF_THE_WYRM">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>At 1st level, you gain a gift of draconic scales from your patron. Parts of your skin are covered by a thin sheen of dragon-like scales. When you aren't wearing armor, your AC equals 13 + your Dexterity modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Breath of the Wyrm" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_BREATH_OF_THE_WYRM">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>Also starting at 1st level, you can borrow your patron's breath weapon. You have a pool of {@dice d6}s that you spend to exhale the breath weapon. The number of dice in the pool equals 1 + half your warlock level.</p>
			<p>As a bonus action, you can exhale this breath weapon in an area, spending dice from the pool to do so. The maximum number of dice you can spend at once equals your proficiency bonus + 1, divided by two. Roll the dice you spend, add them together, and deal that much damage to each creature in the area. The area and the type of damage are determined by your dragon's entry on the Dragon Kind table.</p>
			<p>Your pool regains all expended dice when you finish a long rest. At 6th level, the area of cone weapons increases by 5 feet and the length of line weapons increases by 10 feet. They increase again this way at 10th and 14th levels.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Expanded Spell List" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_EXPANDED_SPELL_LIST">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>The Dragon lets you choose from an expanded list of spells when you learn a warlock spell. The Dragon Expanded Spells table shows the dragon spells that are added to the warlock spell list for you, along with the spells associated in the table with your dragon's kind.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="The Dragon" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_THE_DRAGON">
		<description>
			<p>1th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>Your patron is an ancient spellcasting dragon, either a chromatic dragon (black, blue, green, red, or white) or a metallic dragon (brass, bronze, copper, gold, or silver). Dragons vary from lawful good to chaotic evil and often have far-reaching, inscrutable goals on account of their extremely long lifespans and great power. Some merely desire agents to help them locate and obtain treasures for their hoard, but most do so for reasons that may only come up once every few decades. Such long periods of inaction are trifling to a dragon. Many ancient dragons have acquired enough magical skill to share their power in a pact. Some aspiring warlocks even make pacts with the dragon goddess Tiamat, making a bargain with one of her five heads in particular and drawing on her power as a dragon rather than as a fiend or goddess.</p>
			<p>You choose the scales of your dragon or determine it randomly, using the Dragon Kind table. Each dragon is associated with a damage type and a breath weapon, as shown on the table. The damage type and type of breath weapon used by your patron is referenced by some of the features of this subclass.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Draconic Essence" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_DRACONIC_ESSENCE">
		<description>
			<p>6th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 6th level, your bond with your patron imbues you with a piece of their magical draconic essence. You have resistance to the damage type dealt by your Breath of the Wynn feature, and when one of your spells or class features deals damage of that type to a creature, you can subject that creature to your patron's terrifying draconic presence. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw against your warlock spell save DC. On a failed saving throw, it becomes {@condition frightened} for 1 minute. The target repeats the saving throw at the end of each of its turns, ending the effect on a success.</p>
			<p>Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Everlasting Scales" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_EVERLASTING_SCALES">
		<description>
			<p>10th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>At 10th level, your patron grants you the ability to draw on the true might of its scales. Before you take damage, you can use your reaction to harden your scales for a brief moment. Until the end of your next turn, you gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage, and immunity to the damage type dealt by your Breath of the Wynn feature.</p>
			<p>Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
	<element name="Wings of Terror" type="Archetype Feature" source="The Elements and Beyond" id="ID_TEB_TEB_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_THE_DRAGON_WINGS_OF_TERROR">
		<description>
			<p>14th-level The Dragon feature</p>
			<p>Starting at 14th level, you can use an action to manifest spectral dragon wings as a symbol of your patron's raw power and magic. The wings are made of your patron's breath weapon energy, such as fire, frost, or lightning. When they appear, you can choose to beat the wings in a wing attack, knocking each creature within 10 feet of you prone and dealing each of them damage of the type dealt by your Breath of the Wynn feature equal to {@dice 2d6} + your Charisma modifier (minimum +1), and flying up to half your speed to an unoccupied space.</p>
			<p>Then, whether you performed a wing attack or not, the wings' appearance casts a frightening presence over the battlefield. Each creature of your choice within 60 feet of you that is aware ofyou must make a Wisdom saving throw against your warlock spell save DC. On a failed saving throw, a creature becomes {@condition frightened} for 1 minute. It repeats the saving throw at the end of each of its turns, ending the effect on itself on a success.</p>
			<p>The wings remain for 1 minute, granting you a flying speed equal to your walking speed.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
	</element>
</elements>
